(Raj:)You know, he might not reopen.
(Raj:)He didn't get a lot of money
from the insurance company.
(Sheldon:)Oh, boy, if there is one thing
that gets my goat,
(Sheldon:)it's those dad-gum
insurance companies.
(Leonard:)Why? Because they won't
get off your lawn?
Oh, is Stuart trying to get a
loan, or-or find investors?
(Howard:)All I know is,
he's got my mother
(Howard:)buying four-ply toilet paper.
I mean, four-ply.
(Howard:)If his butt is so delicate,
(Howard:)why doesn't he just use
an angora rabbit?
(Sheldon:)For starters,
they shed and bite.
LEONARD:
Hey,
(Leonard:)here's a thought.
(Leonard:)Why don't we put up the rest
of the money that Stuart needs?
(Raj:)So, we'd be, like, owners
of a comic book store?
(all chuckling)
(Leonard:)It's kind of a
dream come true.
(Howard:)That does sound fun.
(Raj:)Ooh, maybe we could come up
(Raj:)with a business plan
to compete with this place.
(Sheldon:)I'll give you a plan right now.
Step one:
open comic book store.